(Raj:)Hey.
(Raj:)Hey, Leonard, will you
please tell Howard
my sister has never
been attracted to him?
(Leonard:)Come on, Raj,
(Leonard:)how am I supposed to know
who she is attracted to
or was attracted to
(Leonard:)or who she might be
attracted to in the future?
(Sheldon:)And I have nothing
to contribute
(Sheldon:)to this conversation.
(Sheldon:)Because I, too,
know absolutely nothing
(Sheldon:)about Priya's preferences
in male companionship.
(Sheldon:)And with that,
I will re-zip my lip.
(Raj:)Hey, so what did
you guys think
of the new episode
of Caprica last night?
(Leonard:)I didn't see it.
(Howard:)Didn't see it?
(Howard:)What were you doing?
(Leonard:)Uh, I was out.
What, on Caprica night?
(Leonard:)Yeah, I, uh, went
for a drink.
Really, you?
Where, w-where'd
you go?
(Leonard:)To, uh...